let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "The full form of CSS is?",
        answer: "A. Cascading style sheet",
        options: [
           "A. Cascading style sheet",
            "B. Colored special sheet",
            "C. color and style sheet",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "How can we change the background color of an element?",
        answer: "B. Background-color",
        options: [
            "A. Color",
            "B. Background-color",
            "C. Both A and B",
           "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: " In how many ways can CSS be written in?",
        answer: "C. 3",
        options: [
            "A. 1",
            "B. 2",
            "C. 3",
            "D. 4"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How can we write comments in CSS?",
        answer: "B. /*/*",
        options: [
            "A. //",
            "B. /*/*",
            "C. #",
            "D. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which element is used to styling HTML5 layout",
        answer: "A. css",
        options: [
            "A. css",
            "B. jQuery",
            "C.javascript",
            "D. PHP"
        ]
    },
   
        {
            numb: 6,
            question: "What is the smallest header in HTML by default?",
            answer: "C.No",
            options: [
               "A.Yes",
               "B.Depends on property",
               "C.No",
               "D.None of the above"
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 7,
            question: "Which CSS property is used to specify different border styles?",
            answer: "A. border-style",
            options: [
                "A. border-style",
                "B. border",
                "C. Both A and B ",
                "D. None of the above "
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 8,
            question: " How to create an ordered list in HTML?",
            answer: "D. All of the above",
            options: [
                "A.Static",
                "B.Relative",
                "C.Fixed",
                "D. All of the above"
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 9,
            question: "Which of the following CSS property is used for controlling the layout?",
            answer: "B.Display",
            options: [
                "A. color",
                "B.Display",
                "C. text",
                "D.None of the above "
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 10,
            question: "Which of the following are parts of the CSS box model?",
            answer: "D. All of the above",
            options: [
                "A. Margin",
                "B. Borders",
                "C. Padding",
                "D. All of the above"
            ]
        }

    
];
